(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
サインはB
The sign is B
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB
The sign is B
(Chu!)
うりゃ！おい！　うりゃ！おい！
Urya! Oi! Urya! Oi!
B小町！　B小町！
B-Komachi! B-Komachi!
ようやく会えたね　嬉しいね
We finally met, I'm so happy
待ち遠しくて　足をバタバタしながら
Waiting so long, kicking my legs back and forth
今日を楽しみで　眠れなかったよ
I was looking forward to today so much I couldn't sleep
行くぞー！
Let's go!
ARE YOU READY?
OH MY GOD!
緊張なんかしてる　場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous
一分一秒　無駄になんてできない
I can't waste a single minute or second
さあ始めましょう
Now let's begin
君も君も君も　お待たせ様
You and you and you, sorry to keep you waiting
手を鳴らせ　いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome
好きが集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where love gathers
日常は　グルグルの中
Everyday life is in a whirl
ここに来たなら　踊り明かそう
Since you've come here, let's dance the night away
(Saa! Saa! Saa!)
人混みも今は関係ない
The crowds don't matter now
ハコが大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる　君のサイリウム
I can see your glowstick clearly
今振れば振れば飛ぶような
Now if you wave it, if you wave it, it'll fly
ちっちゃなちっちゃな才能だけど
It's a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you'll support me
バクレスをあげる
I'll give you a response
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB
The sign is B
(Chu!)
うりゃ！おい！　うりゃ！おい！
Urya! Oi! Urya! Oi!
B小町！　B小町！
B-Komachi! B-Komachi!
アイツは俺が育てたって
That girl, I'm the one who raised her
近い将来　自慢してほしい
I want you to brag about it in the near future
こうしちゃいられない
I can't just stay like this
君と君と　今を楽しまなきゃ
I have to enjoy the moment with you and you
引きこもりも　人見知りも
The shut-ins and the shy ones
普段と違う顔　見せてよ
Show me a different face than usual
みんな兄弟　調子はどうだい？
Everyone's brothers, how's it going?
なりふり構わずに
Without caring how you look
(Saa! Saa! Saa!)
人に笑われても関係ない
It doesn't matter if people laugh at you
迷い踊るのポーズとか気にしない
Don't care about the poses when dancing around
しちゃおう　強すぎ　君のサイリウム
Let's show off your overwhelming glowstick
たとえ世界が私を拒み
Even if the world rejects me
独りぼっち感じたとしても
And I feel all alone
あなたが見守ってくれたら
If you watch over me
怖いものはないよ
There's nothing to be afraid of
B小町！　B小町！
B-Komachi! B-Komachi!
見てよ　見てよ　何かが始まる
Look, look, something is starting
君との物語が
The story with you
あぁなんて　素晴らしい景色だ
Ah, what a wonderful sight
人がいようがいまいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if people are there or not
ハコが大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる　君の...
I can see your...
サインはB！
The sign is B!
今ふっと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, if I were to blow, it'd fly away
ちっちゃなちっちゃなサインだけど
It's a tiny, tiny sign, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me,
あなたが向かった先でいてくれたら
if you're there at the destination you headed for,
レスをあげる
I'll give you a shoutout
あなたのア・イ・ド・ル
Your i-d-o-l
サインはB！
The sign is B!
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
今日はボレロ 蕩けちゃって
Today it's a bolero, melt away,
初恋レモン 9割人類パイパパパパイ
First love lemon, 90% of humanity, pai-pa-pa-pa-pai
オープンパスター モレモレよ
Open pasta, it's leaking,
おかわりはアンコール次第ね
Refills depend on the encore, right?
終わらない 愛包ダンスホール
Never-ending Aipai Dance Hall
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
おかわりなら今ほしい
If it's a refill, I want it now
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
3.1415926535のパイだって
Even the pi of 3.1415926535...
割り切れない 気持ち抱えてるよ
holds feelings that can't be neatly divided.
野暮心 下心 親心 演じくんね
Nonsense, ulterior motives, parental love, let's play along
割り切れない 命一世一代のヘブン
An indivisible life, once-in-a-lifetime heaven
今宵いいんじゃない? ほら
Isn't tonight good? Look,
踊ればいいんじゃない? ほら フリフリフラれば
Isn't it fine to dance? Look, if you swing and wave...
人生 幸せ 冷静 結成 旺盛
Life, happiness, calmness, formation, vigorous
汗ばんだら ガンダーラ 燦々ら
If you get sweaty, Gandhara, sparkling
参ってんの? 高まった感情の再会
Are you tired? A reunion of heightened emotions
集まった愛情のWiFi
WiFi of gathered affection
持ち寄った上々の未来 愛してるが重なって
A superb future we brought together, "I love you"s overlapping
狂まった人類の情態 熱いミントパイみたいだね
The crazy state of humanity, like a hot mint pie, isn't it?
パパパパパイ パイ
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pai, pai
愛杯 愛杯で ほれ ほれ よ
Aipai, Aipai, look, look,
蕩けちゃって 初恋レモン 9割人類パイパパパパイ
Melt away, first love lemon, 90% of humanity, pai-pa-pa-pa-pai
乾杯 完済に ほれ ほれ よ
Cheers, fully paid, look, look,
ムロディみたいね 愛包に 頭ん中 ポポラパパパイ
Like a melody, right? In Aipai, inside my head, po-po-ra-pa-pa-pai
鮮やかな脳内 脳裏の煩悩も愛杯か
Vivid inside the brain, are the worldly desires in the mind also Aipai?
イマジン オートピーポーの祭典 ダンスホールザイマジンも披露
Imagine, the festival of auto-people, Dance Hall Imagine reveal
乾杯ね 今日はボレロ 混じり合って 人類パイ頑張って笑って
Cheers, right? Today it's a bolero, mixing together, humanity, do your best and smile
おかわりほしいでしょ?
You want a refill, don't you?
全人類構成物質 都会の目指すべき一日は
The constituent substances of all humanity, the day a city should aim for...
臨時で信じてパイになるような 脳味噌もトロトロのよう
Believing temporarily to become a pie, the brain seems to be melting too
現実 は生涯 オンライン 踊りまして 煩悩 は総退
Reality is online for life, dancing away, worldly desires are all retreating
尽きまして 先人を量産 パパパパパパパパパイ
Exhausted, mass-producing predecessors, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pai
人類最高。のダンスタイム
Humanity's best. Dance time
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
愛杯で 愛包ダンスホール
With Aipai, Aipai Dance Hall
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
僕らが生まれて 初めて知る音は心臓の鼓動だろう
The first sound we learn after being born is likely the heartbeat
トトトントトトントトトンテントトン
To-to-ton to-to-ton to-to-ton ten-to-ton
それはリズムと知った
I learned that it was rhythm
古も今どきも パイビートが僕たちを包んで繋いでんだろう
Ancient or modern, the pi-beat likely wraps and connects us
愛杯 愛杯で ほれ ほれ よ
Aipai, Aipai, look, look,
蕩けちゃって 初恋レモン 9割人類パイパパパパイ
Melt away, first love lemon, 90% of humanity, pai-pa-pa-pa-pai
乾杯 完済に ほれ ほれ よ
Cheers, fully paid, look, look,
ムロディみたいね 愛包に 頭ん中 ポポラパパパイ
Like a melody, right? In Aipai, inside my head, po-po-ra-pa-pa-pai
ラララララララララ まるで煩悩で踊ってるみたい
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la, just like dancing with worldly desires,
生まれ変わったような気分でして
feeling like I've been reborn
乾杯ね 今日はボレロ 混じり合って 人類パイ頑張って笑って
Cheers, right? Today it's a bolero, mixing together, humanity, do your best and smile
寂しいよな 終わりは近づくけどさ
It's lonely, isn't it? The end is drawing near, but...
終わらない パイのように 続けばいい
It'd be nice if it continued like the never-ending pi
計算なんてできないが
I can't do the math, but...
愛杯 愛杯ダンスホール
Aipai, Aipai Dance Hall
今日はボレロ 蕩けちゃって
Today it's a bolero, melt away,
初恋レモン 9割人類パイパパパパイ
First love lemon, 90% of humanity, pai-pa-pa-pa-pai
無茶苦茶にしにきてね
Come and make a mess of things,
あなたならいつでもいいよ
anytime is fine if it's you.
おかわりほしいでしょ?
You want a refill, don't you?
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
おかわりならもほしい
I want another refill too
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
ということで始まりました、かなけん3Dライブ！
And with that, the Kanaken 3D Live has begun!
はい。ということで、まずは自己紹介をね、させていただきます。
Yes. So, first of all, we'll introduce ourselves.
はい。それではあずちゃんから！
Yes. Then, starting with AZ-chan!
はい！右手にマイク、左手に地図。
Yes! A microphone in my right hand, a map in my left hand.
あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー。AZKiです！
I'm the Zero-Guesser for your heart. I'm AZKi!
AZKiです、かなけん社員です!
I'm AZKi, a Kanaken employee!
あと秘書です!
And I'm the secretary!
おお～!
Oh!
いつから秘書になったんだろう。
When did she become secretary?
素晴らしい。
Wonderful.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
はい。とてもいい女ということで。
Yes. As a very fine woman.
それでは次は、沙花叉!
Now, next is Sakamata!
はい!
Yes!
バクバクバク～ン!
Baku baku bakun!
秘密結社holoXの掃除屋、インターン社員の沙花叉クロヱです!
I'm the cleaner of Secret Society holoX, intern Sakamata Chloe!
かなけん副社長です!
I'm Kanaken's vice president!
いつから副社長?!
Since when were you vice president?!
いつから副社長になったんだ?
Since when did she become vice president?
そうですよ!
That's right!
偶然二番目に入れたんだから!
Because I happened to join second!
二番目?
Second?
二番目だから副社長なんだ。
Because you're second, you're vice president.
副社長なの! よろしくお願いします。
I'm vice president! Nice to meet you.
ありがとうございます。はい、それでは最後は...
Thank you. Yes, and finally...
キャッチコピーは握力50キロ、ギュギュっと握りつぶしちゃうぞ。
Catchphrase: 50kg grip strength. I'll squeeze you tight.
ホロライブ四期生、天音かなたです!
Hololive 4th Gen, Amane Kanata!
かなけん社長しております!
I'm the Kanaken president!
よっ、社長!
Hey, President!
一番偉いです!
The highest ranking!
そう、一番偉い、はず。
Yes, the highest ranking, I should be.
はずじゃない、一番偉い!
Not 'should be', I am!
一番偉いです。
She is the highest ranking.
そんな感じで盛りだくさんの3Dライブ、
With that, I hope everyone enjoys
ぜひみんなにも楽しんでほしいと思います!
this jam-packed 3D live!
イェーイ!
Yay!
はい、ガンガン盛り上がっていきましょう!
Yes, let's get hyped up!
行きましょう!
Let's go!
ということで、次の曲は「Habit」!
So, the next song is "Habit"!
Habit / 作詞: Fukase 作曲: Nakajin
Habit / Lyrics: Fukase, Composition: Nakajin
君たちったら何でもかんでも 分類、区別、ジャンル分けしたがる
You guys always want to classify,
distinguish, and categorize everything
人はなぜか分類したがる 習性があるとかないとか
People somehow have a habit
of wanting to classify, or so they say
この世の中に数種類の人間が いるとか言う君たちが標的
You who say there are only a few types
of people in this world are the targets
持ってる奴と持ってない奴とか ちゃんとやる奴とやってない奴とか
Those who have and those who don't,
those who do things properly and those who don't
陰キャ陽キャ君らは分類 しないとどうにも落ち着かない
Introverts, extroverts - you can't
settle down unless you classify them
気づかない本能の外側を 覗いてごらんよ気分が乗らない?
Try peeking outside the instincts you
don't notice. Aren't you in the mood?
つまり それはそんなシンプルじゃない
In other words, it's not that simple
もっと曖昧で繊細で不明瞭な何か
Something more ambiguous,
delicate, and unclear
例えば持ってるのに出さない奴 合ってるのにいけない奴
For example, those who have it but don't show it,
those who are right but can't go through with it
持ってるのに悟ったふりして 透かしてるうちに不安になっちゃったりする奴
Those who pretend to be enlightened, getting
anxious while trying to act cool
正味あんたギフテッド
To be honest, "You're gifted,
あたしは普通の主婦です、と
I'm just an ordinary housewife."
それはいいでしょう 素晴らしいでしょう
That's fine, right? That's wonderful, right?
不可能の証明の完成なんじゃない?
Isn't that the completion of the proof
of impossibility?
夢を持てなんて言ってない
I'm not saying you should have a dream
そんな無責任になりはしない
I won't be that irresponsible
ただその習性に食われないで そんなハビット捨てるたび見えてくる
Just don't be eaten by that habit. Every time
you throw away that habit, it becomes visible
君の価値
Your value
俺たちだって動物
We're animals too
こういうのが大好物
We love this kind of thing
ここまで言われたらドブネズミ 腹の底からこみ上げるフツフツと
After being told this much, like gutter rats,
something wells up from the bottom of the heart
俺たちだって動物
We're animals too
ゆえに持つオリジナルな習性
Thus we have original habits
自分で自分を分類するなよ
Don't classify yourself
壊して見せろよそのバッドハビット
Break it and show us, that bad habit
大人の俺が言っちゃいけないこと言っちゃうけど
I'll say what an adult like me
shouldn't say, but
説教するってぶっちゃけ快楽
preaching is, to be honest, a pleasure
酒の肴にすりゃもう傑作
If you make it a snack for your drink,
it's a masterpiece
でもって君も進むきっかけに
And if it gives you a chance
to move forward
なりゃそりゃそれでウィンウィンじゃん
then that's a win-win, isn't it?
こりゃこれで残念じゃん
This is disappointing in its own way
そもそもそれって君次第だし
Anyway, that's up to you, and
その後なんか俺興味ないわけ
I have no interest in what happens after
この先君はどうしたい?
The fact itself that people ask you
って人に問われること自体
"What do you want to do from now on?"
終わりじゃないと信じたい
I want to believe it's not the end,
けどそうじゃなきゃかなり大惨事
but if it's not, it's quite a catastrophe
君たちがその分類された
Because you guys are smoldering
普通の箱でくすぶってるからさ
in that classified ordinary box
俺は人生イージーモード
Life is easy mode for me
ずっとそこで眠っててくれよな
Stay asleep there forever, okay?
俺はそもそもスペックが低い
I have low specs to begin with
だからあがいてもがいて醜く吠えて
So I struggle, writhe, and howl uglily
俺のあの頃を分類したら
If you classify my back then,
誰の目から見ても明らか
it's obvious to anyone's eyes
すぐ世の中金だとか愛だとか
Quickly saying the world is about
運だとか縁だとか
money, love, luck, or fate
なぜに文字で片付けちゃうの
Why do you settle it with words?
俺たちはもっと曖昧で
We are more ambiguous
複雑で明瞭な何か
Something complex and clear
悟ったふりして奢るなよ
Don't pretend to be enlightened
and be arrogant
君に君を分類する能力なんてない
You don't have the ability to
classify yourself
俺たちだって動物
We're animals too
こういうのが大好物
We love this kind of thing
ここまで言われたらドブネズミ 腹の底からこみ上げるフツフツと
After being told this much, like gutter rats,
something wells up from the bottom of the heart
俺たちだって動物
We're animals too
ゆえに持つオリジナルな習性
Thus we have original habits
自分で自分を分類するなよ
Don't classify yourself
壊して見せろよそのバッドハビット
Break it and show us, that bad habit
俺たちだって動物
We're animals, too
こういうのって好物
We love this kind of thing
ここまで言われたらドM
If you say all that, I must be a masochist
腹の底からコブシ
A guttural shout from the bottom of my stomach
そう、俺たちだって動物
That's right, we're animals, too
故に持論自論に縛られな、習性
So don't be bound by your own theories—it's just a habit
自分で自分を分類するなよ
Don't go classifying yourself
壊して見せるよ、そのBad Habit
I'll show you I can break that bad habit
晴る
天音かなた、沙花叉クロヱ、AZKi
作詞・作曲：n-buna
Sunny
Vocals: Amane Kanata, Sakamata Chloe, AZKi
Lyrics/Composition: n-buna
あなたは風のように 目を閉じては夕暮れ
You're like the wind, closing your eyes at dusk
何を思っているんだろうか
I wonder what you're thinking about
瞼を開いていた あなたの目にビイドロ
Your eyelids were open, like glass in your eyes
今少しだけ晴れの匂いがした
Just now, it smelled a bit like clear weather
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け さあ、出で晴るの背
Shine and shine, bloom, oh flowers! Come now, the back of the clear sky
降りやめば雨でさえ あなたを飾る晴る
If it stops raining, even the rain is a clearing sky that decorates you
胸を打つ音よ鳴れ 暴力的な春風
Let the sound that strikes the heart ring out, oh violent spring breeze
あの雲も越えて行け 遠くまで 遠くまで
Go even beyond those clouds, far away, far away
あなたは晴れ模様に 目を閉じては青色
You're in a clear sky, closing your eyes to the blue
何が悲しいんだろうか
I wonder what's so sad
瞼を開いていた あなたの目にビイドロ
Your eyelids were open, like glass in your eyes
今少し雨の匂いがした
Just now, it smelled a bit like rain
泣きに泣け、空よ鳴け さあ、出で晴るの背
Cry and cry, oh sky, cry out! Come now, the back of the clear sky
降りしきる雨でさえ 雲の上では晴る
Even the pouring rain is a clearing sky above the clouds
土を打つ音よ鳴れ 暴力的な晴れに
Let the sound hitting the earth ring out in the violent clear sky
あの海も越えて行く 遠くまで 遠くまで
Going even beyond that sea, far away, far away
通り雨、草も靡かせて 羊雲、あれも晴るの背
A passing shower, making the grass sway; altocumulus clouds, they too are the back of the clear sky
風のよう、胸に晴るの背
Like the wind, the back of the clear sky in my heart
晴るを待つ
Waiting for the sky to clear
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け さあ、出で晴るの背
Shine and shine, bloom, oh flowers! Come now, the back of the clear sky
降りやめば雨でさえ あなたを飾る晴る
If it stops raining, even the rain is a clearing sky that decorates you
胸を打つ音よ奏で 暴力的な春風
Let the sound that strikes the heart play out, oh violent spring breeze
音に聞く晴るの風 さあ、この歌よ鳴れ
The clearing wind heard in sound; now, let this song ring out
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け さあ、出で晴るの背
Shine and shine, bloom, oh flowers! Come now, the back of the clear sky
あの雲も越えて行く
Beyond those clouds we go
遠くまだ遠くまで
Farther, still farther away
ビビデバ
Bibideba
Come on, my days もう散々ね
Come on, my days, it's been terrible
奇跡願ってるだけの人生
A life of just wishing for miracles
Watch me, dut-dut-dut-ta-hit you
虜にしましょう Magic
Let me captivate you with magic
I wanna be free だって I wanna be free
I wanna be free, because I wanna be free
ちょっとはにかんで Step out
Bashfully stepping out
エトセトラ 宇宙まで
And so on, to the ends of space
秒針は音を立てて
The second hand makes its sound
夜を急かす魔物のよう
Like a monster rushing the night
人生は一瞬にして 解ける魔法
Life is a magic spell that breaks in an instant
それならば 駆け抜けて 思い通り
If that's the case, run through it just as you wish
お邪魔な鎖飛び乗って Driving
Jumping onto those meddling chains, driving
私は大変身 Make up
I'm undergoing a major transformation, make up
我がままの Money money 煌めきに Change
Selfish money, money, changing into a sparkle
しゃらくな街で Dancing
Dancing in this cheeky city
さよなら Goodbye Let it go
Say goodbye, goodbye, let it go
いつかは喝采 Crowd the audience
Someday, cheers will fill the crowd
皆々ご唱和あれ
Everyone, sing along with me
Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Yeah!
後悔したってしょうがないから
There's no point in regretting it
シューズ辿る Tonight
Following my shoes tonight
Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Yeah!
今夜にアスナロはないならば
If there's no "tomorrow" for tonight
自由取ったもん勝ちでしょ
Then winning is all about taking your freedom
Dut-dut-da-down Slide a-di-ho
どんな問題も会話ひとつ
Every problem is just one conversation away
拍手も正解も間違いも
The applause, the right answers, the mistakes too
愛す本当の私の理想
I'll love them all, my true ideal
あの高い世界は限界の気配がして
That high world feels like it's reaching its limit
おどおど安心じゃ心配
Just being timidly safe makes me worried
今すぐ Jumping Jumping Now!
Now, jumping, jumping, now!
チキチキバンバン チキバンバン
Chiki chiki ban ban, chiki ban ban
逆々ニキニキ 回抱く日々に
Back and forth, side by side, in days of recovery
ギリギリ爆発 君だって
On the verge of exploding, even you
今 発散してしまおうか
Shall we let it all out right now?
まだまだ Bibide-babide-boo-wa!
More and more, Bibide-babide-boo-wa!
1発じゃ足りないわ
One shot isn't enough
ついに導き出した 君にアンサー
Finally I've found it, the answer for you
灰になるまで踊ってよ
Dance until we turn to ash
お邪魔な鎖飛び乗って Driving
Jumping onto those meddling chains, driving
私は大変身 Make up
I'm undergoing a major transformation, make up
我がままの Money money 煌めきに Change
Selfish money, money, changing into a sparkle
しゃらくな街で Dancing
Dancing in this cheeky city
さよなら Goodbye Let it go
Say goodbye, goodbye, let it go
いつかは喝采 Crowd the audience
Someday, cheers will fill the crowd
皆々ご唱和あれ
Everyone, sing along with me
Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Yeah!
後悔したってしょうがないから
There's no point in regretting it
シューズ辿る Tonight
Following my shoes tonight
Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Bibide-babide-boo-wa! Yeah!
今夜にアスナロはないならば
If there's no "tomorrow" for tonight
自由取ったもん勝ちでしょ
Then winning is all about taking your freedom
ノーザンクロス
Northern Cross
旅の始まりは もう思い出せない
I can no longer remember the start of the journey
気づいたら ここにいた
Before I knew it, I was here
季節が破けて 見果てぬ先が
The seasons have torn open, and the endless future...
閃光 感じる瞳が 迷子になる
...makes my eyes that feel the flash get lost
たぶん失うのだ 命だけの思い
Perhaps I will lose it, this feeling that is my very life
戦うように恋した
I loved as if I were fighting
ひたすらに夢を追った
I chased my dreams single-mindedly
その星より高かった
It was higher than that star
君の空 飛びたかった
I wanted to fly in your sky
誰か空虚の輪郭を そっとなでてくれないか
Won't someone gently stroke the outline of the void?
胸の鼓動に蹴飛ばされて
Kicked by the beating of my heart
転がり出た愛の言葉
The words of love tumbled out
だけど困ったな 答えがない
But I'm in trouble, there's no answer
宿命に張り付けられた
Pinned down by destiny
北極星が燃えてる
The North Star is burning
君を拒否して 凍らせた
I rejected you and froze you
なのに 可憐に花を咲かす
And yet, it blooms so gracefully
好きだったよ
I loved you
君がいないなら
If you are not here
意味なんてなくなるから
Then everything loses its meaning
人は全部冷えればいい
So everyone should just turn cold
愛がなくなれば
If love disappears
心だっていらないから
Then I don't even need a heart
この世界も消えてしまえ
This world should just vanish as well
ずっと苦しかった
I've been suffering for a long time
命がけの出会い
A life-risking encounter
もがくように夢見た
I dreamed as if struggling
闇雲に手を伸ばした
I reached out blindly
そのまでに気づきたかった
I wanted to realize it by then
君と虹を架けたかった
I wanted to build a rainbow with you
誰か夜明けの感傷で
Someone, with the sentiment of dawn
ぎゅっと抱いてくれないか
Won't you hold me tight?
夢が軌道に弾かれて
Dreams were bounced off their orbit
飛び散るだけの愛の涙
Only tears of love scattering
それがむき出しの痛みでもいい
Even if it's raw pain, it's fine
宿命に呼び戻された
Called back by destiny
北極星が泣いている
The North Star is crying
どうせ見えない行方なら
If the destination is invisible anyway
君を包むまで愛して
I'll love you until I envelop you
死にたいよ
I want to die
そして始まるのだ
And so it begins
命がけの終わり
A life-risking end
戦うように愛した
I loved as if fighting
ぐしゃぐしゃに夢を蹴った
I kicked my dreams into a mess
その星に果てたかった
I wanted to perish on that star
君の空咲きたかった
I wanted to bloom in your sky
誰か虚空の輪郭を
Someone, the outline of the void
そっとなでてくれないか
Won't you gently stroke it?
時の波にかき消されて
Drowned out by the waves of time
救えなかった愛の言葉
Words of love that couldn't be saved
だからもう一度答えが欲しい
So I want an answer once more
宿命に張り付けられた
Crucified to destiny
北極星が燃えている
The North Star is burning
君を焼きしめて凍らした
I scorched you and made you freeze
なのに可憐に笑う此処
Yet here you laugh so prettily
君を焼きしめて凍らした
I scorched you and made you freeze
なのに可憐に笑う此処
Yet here you laugh so prettily
好きだったよ
I loved you
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world
そういう扱い心得て
Understand that's how you should treat me
よね！
Right?
ワールドイズマイン
WORLD IS MINE
作詞・作曲・編曲：ryo
World is Mine
WORLD IS MINE
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: ryo
その一、いつもと違う髪型に気が付くこと
Number one: notice when my hairstyle is different from usual
その二、ちゃんと靴まで見ること、いいね？
Number two: make sure you look down to my shoes, okay?
その三、私の一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Number three: reply to every word of mine with three of yours
わかったら右手がお留守なのを
If you understand, then do something about
なんとかして！
my neglected right hand!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything
君に心から思ってほしいの、かわいいって
I just want you to think from your heart that I'm cute
それとね、白いお馬さん、決まってるでしょ？
迎えに来て
And also, a white horse, you've decided on one, right?
Come pick me up
わかったら、かしずいて手を取って
「お姫様」って
If you understand, kneel, take my hand,
and call me "Princess"
別にわがままなんて言ってない。だから...
It's not like I'm being selfish. So...
でもね、少しぐらい叱ってくれたっていいのよ
But you know, it's okay if you scold me just a little
世界で私だけのお王子様、気がついて
My one and only prince in the world, notice me
ほらほら、おててが空いてます
Look, look, my hands are free
無口で不愛想な王子様、もうどうして！
My silent and unsociable prince, oh why!
気がついてよ早く！
Notice me already!
ぜったい君は分かってない！
You definitely don't understand!
分かってないわ...
You don't understand...
苺の乗ったショートケーキ
Shortcake with strawberries on top
こだわり卵のとろけるプリン
Melting pudding made with special eggs
みんな、みんな我慢します...
わがままな子だと思わないで
I'll endure them all...
Don't think of me as a selfish girl
私だってやればできるもん
I can do it if I try
あとで後悔するわよ
You'll regret it later
当然です！ だって私は...
Of course! Because I am...
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world
ちゃんと見ててよね、どこかに行っちゃうよ？
Look at me properly, or I'll go somewhere else, you know?
ふいに抱きしめられた、急に「そんな、えっ！」
Suddenly I was hugged, out of the blue "That, what!"
「轢かれる、危ないよ」そう言ってそっぽ向く君
"You'll get run over, it's dangerous," you say, turning away
こっちのが危ないわよ！
This is more dangerous!
はーい！ということでお聴きいただいたのは、Habit、
Hi! So, the songs you just heard were Habit,
春を告げる、ビビデバ、ノーザンクロス、
ワールドイズマインでした！
Haru wo Tsugeru, Bibideba, Northern Cross,
and World is Mine!
いえーい！ どうだったかなー？
Yay! How was it?
はい、ありがとうございます！ ここからも...
Yes, thank you! From here on as well...
うん、ここからも、ここからもね！
Yeah, from here on, from here on too!
怒涛のかなけんパワーを見せていくので、
最後までついてきてください！
We're going to show you the relentless Kanaken power,
so please stay with us until the end!
いぇーい！
Yay!
それでは、次はAZKi先輩のオリジナル楽曲
「Intersection」を歌わせていただきます！
And now, we'll be singing AZKi-senpai's original song,
"Intersection"!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
気にしないでなんて言わないで
Don't say "don't mind it"
ホントはいつも正直じゃないけど
Honestly I'm never straightforward but
気がついてよなんて言えなくて
I can't say "please notice me"
嘘ばかり
Just telling lies
Can't stop love with you 溺れたいな
Can't stop love with you, I want to drown
I gotcha ぎゅっと 填まる君の交差点
I gotcha tight, stuck in your intersection
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings more
Yellow ちょいアブないね
Yellow, it's a bit dangerous
Knock it out!
Knock it out! 鳴らせ鐘を 先駆け撃ち 最強
Knock it out! Ring the bell, shoot first, strongest
Knock it out! Knocking it out! Hey Hey!
それフェイク(笑) はい にゃんにゃんにゃー V
That's a fake (lol) Yes, nyan nyan nyan V
無敵なアイ・アイ・アイ・会いたいな
Invincible love, love, love, I want to see you
着飾れほらピース うらびれ落ちる
Dress up, look, peace, falling into despair
ナイ・ナイ・ナイ・意味ない
No, no, no, it's meaningless
ガンショー 燃やせプライド
Gunshow, burn your pride
擬態じゃんごっこ いいねもっと
Mimicry play, like it more
つまんない嘘 距離のシンデレラ
A boring lie, the distance's Cinderella
「叶えたい」 消えたい 歪んでいくんだ
"I want it to come true", I want to disappear, it's getting distorted
僕と僕との境界線
The boundary between me and myself
どれも正解で！
Any of them is the right answer!
どれも正解だ！
叶えたい 消えたい 歪んでいくんだ
僕と僕との境界線
I want it to come true, I want to disappear, it's getting distorted
The boundary between me and myself
ドクドクドク ドクドクドク
Thump thump thump thump thump thump
さよならはもう 興味ない
I'm no longer interested in goodbyes
ドクドクドク ドクドクドク
Thump thump thump thump thump thump
愛すれば あたしのタイム 奪っておいて
If I love, steal my time
無駄 結論非効率だね
Useless, the conclusion is it's inefficient
限界 モード・ク 活かして頂戴
面倒なアコガレの相手
Limit, Mode-Ku, please make use of it
The troublesome person I admire
面倒ね　アコガレの相手
It's a pain, the person I admire.
嫌い　嫌い　嫌い　嫌い
I hate you, hate you, hate you, hate you.
ズルいっちゃダメなのはワレモノね
Being unfair is for fragile things, isn't it?
モードドク　至って冷静
Mode-Doku, perfectly calm.
表情も変えないで冷淡
Without changing expression, indifferent.
嫌い　嫌い　嫌い　嫌い
I hate you, hate you, hate you, hate you.
笑っちゃダメなのは残酷ね
Not being allowed to laugh is cruel, isn't it?
綺麗なようですね
You seem to be beautiful.
素敵なドクドクミュージック
Wonderful thumping music.
おらくる
Oracle
あらくら　めくるめくときめきになれ
Ara-kura, become a dizzying heartbeat.
普遍的なチェンジ　なるなる　愛したげるね
A universal change is coming, I'll love you.
大丈夫　どんどんやって満たして
It's okay, keep doing it and fill me up.
ブクブクに凝ってこらして
Bubbling up, focusing deeply.
たあんと　I love you
Plenty of I love you.
ω猫
ω Neko
ボクが一番カワイイにゃん！
I'm the cutest, meow!
君とずっとずっといたいので
I want to be with you forever and ever...
ボクに首輪をしといてね？
...so put a collar on me, okay?
理屈ってないね　そんなの無くたって
There's no logic, even without that...
ボクは君の運命のにゃん
...I'm your cat of destiny, meow.
夢がさめてしまうまで
Until the dream wakes up...
鈴の鳴るたびかまってね？
...pay attention to me every time the bell rings, okay?
君の愛のぜんぶをください
Give me all of your love.
そしたらぜったい　にゃんにゃん！な法！
Then it'll definitely be meow meow law!
にゃんってかまって　にゃんにゃん！
Meow, pay attention to me, meow meow!
特者生存ワンダラだー!!
Tokusha Seizon Wonder-la!!
猪突猛進！　ちゃんと冒険して
Headlong rush! Venture properly.
荒唐無稽！　ちゃんと空想して
Absurd! Imagine properly.
楽しもう
Let's enjoy.
“努力とは最後まで諦めないこと”
"Effort means not giving up until the end."
メモっておいて！
Take a note of that!
いのち (2024 ver)
Inochi (2024 ver)
最後まで私のこと覚えててくれるの？
Will you remember me until the end?
消えてしまいそうなの　わかってよ　わかってよねえ
It feels like I'm going to disappear, understand me, understand me, hey.
本当のとこどうなの？　いずれは卒業するんでしょう？
What's the truth? You'll graduate eventually, right?
日常に戻ったら　私は居なくなるの
When things go back to normal, I'll be gone.
命のような夢を見てるよ
I'm having a dream like life itself.
またねバイバイ
See you, bye bye.
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Jinsei Reset Button Pochi-w
あたし　ジャンクフードなし思考回路
I'm a thought process without junk food.
混ざる　退廃的な異常行動
Mixing, decadent abnormal behavior.
待たしたい　惑わしたい　構わしたい　踏みつけたいなら
If you want to make me wait, mislead me, make me care, trample me...
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
life reset button, click-w.
人生リセットの段落ちー
Life reset drop-off.
品性に欠け冗談きーw
Lacking dignity, joke-y-w.
人生リセットボタンぽちー
Life reset button, click.
WORKING... WORKING... WORK... WORK...
「これは、3人の社員による、果てなき労働の物語である」
"This is a story of endless labor by three employees."
天界級オシゴトロード
Tenkai Kyuukyuu Oshigoto Road
社員番号 No.3 超大型新人 AZKi
Employee number No. 3, super-sized rookie AZKi.
先輩だけどマジ後輩　天然キャラなんて誤解誤解
Senior but totally a junior, "natural airhead" is a total misunderstanding.
イケイケゴーゴー　詰まったら即セーブ＆ロード
Go go go! If you're stuck, save and load immediately.
今日も現場へ急行　でもそろそろ払ってね給与！
Rushing to the site today too, but pay my salary soon!
社員番号 No.2 スーパー秘書登場 沙花叉クロヱ
Employee number No. 2, super secretary appears, Sakamata Chloe.
大きな御口でバクバク　なんだって食べちゃうぞバクッ！
Munching with a big mouth, I'll eat anything, chomp!
特徴は生意気スキル　お風呂キャンセル特濃スメル
Features: cheeky skill, bath cancellation, extra-strong smell.
もう実質副社長　気を抜いたらやっちゃう下克上
I'm practically the Vice President, I'll stage a coup if you let your guard down.
社員番号 No.1 社長だよ かなた
Employee number No. 1, it's the President, Kanata.
美人でキュートで声が最高で　笑顔で清楚でボクっ娘で
Beautiful, cute, best voice, smiling, neat, uses "boku"...
オシャレでセクシー　スタイル抜群
...fashionable and sexy, outstanding style.
愛情たっぷりボンキュッボン！
Full of love, curvy body!
とにかく凄えぞかなた社長！
Anyway, President Kanata is amazing!
最強無敵3人で　明るい未来作りましょう
The strongest, invincible three, let's build a bright future.
やりがいだらけそれゆけ
Full of job satisfaction, let's go.
誇り高きオシゴトロード
Proud Work Road.
推せ推せよ (Yeah!) 声出せよ (Hey!)
Push push (Yeah!), shout out (Hey!).
ラブを心に抱け
Embrace love in your heart.
今見せよ (Yeah!) 光らせよ (Hey!)
Show it now (Yeah!), let it shine (Hey!).
ロマンスを捧げて
Offer your romance.
ハチャメチャで (Hey!) スチャラカで
Hectic (Hey!), happy-go-lucky...
めちゃくちゃ頑張って生きやんせ (Hey!)
...give it your all and live (Hey!).
ルール違反したら握り潰しちゃうぞ
If you break the rules, I'll crush you.
ギュッギュッギュッギュッギュッギュッギュ
Squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze.
全世界の推し事中のみなさん、こんにちは、こんばんは、おはようございまーす
Hello, good evening, good morning to everyone in the world who is fanning!
今日もみんな元気にモリモリ働いて
Everyone work hard and healthily today too.
「今日もみんな元気にりもり、働いてえらい！」
"Today too, everyone is working hard with high spirits, you're doing great!"
「推しの幸せは？」
"What is your oshi's happiness?"
「そう！自分の幸せ！」
"That's right! My own happiness!"
「つーわけで、働け労働！」
"So, work, laborers!"
サーイエッサー！
Sir, yes, sir!
どっこいしょ！ どっこいしょ！
Dokkoisho! Dokkoisho!
どっこい どっこい どっこいしょ！
Dokkoi dokkoi dokkoisho!
Everybody Road Go Fight Day Oh!
「脳天カチ割る声を出せ〜！」
"Let out a voice that splits the crown of your head!"
AZKi 開拓者！ これが限界アリーナツアー
AZKi, Pioneer! This is the limit, arena tour
沙花叉 飼育員！ ぶち上げDJ B2B
Sakamata, Keeper! Hyping it up, DJ B2B
かなた へい民！ 全員見てんぞ永遠に
Kanata, Heimin! Everyone's watching forever
天界等級オンザロード
Tenkai Toukyuu On the Road
WORKING! WORKING! WAR!
推せ推せよ
Push it, push it
Yeah!
声出せよ
Let out your voice
Yeah! Hey!
なんたってアイドルだからね
Because we're idols, after all
沼ハマって
Fall into the swamp
Yeah! 床になって
Yeah! Become the floor
Hey!
ロマンスを捧げて
Offer your romance
夢見たいな
I want to see a dream
Yeah! 世界見たいな
Yeah! I want to see the world
Hey!
みんなで一緒に叶えよう
Let's fulfill it together with everyone
ルール違反したら
If you break the rules
握り潰しちゃうぞ
I'll crush you
ギュッギュッギュッギュッギュッギュッ
Gyu gyu gyu gyu gyu gyu
WORKING... WORKING...
はい、みなさーん！
Hi, everyone!
はーい！
Hi!
やり遂げましたね！
We did it!
ついに、かなけんのオリジナル楽曲ができました！
Finally, Kanaken's original song is finished!
イェーイ！
Yay!
シャカシャカシャカシャカ...
Shaka shaka shaka...
はい、もうね、本当待望だよね。
Yes, it's really long-awaited, isn't it?
ずっと作りたいって言ってて、やっと形になりました。
We've been saying we wanted to make one, and it finally took shape.
やっと、本当に形になりました！
Finally, it has really taken shape!
やっとですよ！
Finally!
みんな盛り上がってくれて、本当にありがとう！
Everyone got hyped up, thank you so much!
どうだったかな？ めっちゃ労働してますね。
How was it? We're working really hard.
そうですよ、本当に。やっちゃってますね。
That's right, really. We're doing it.
ブラックですよ、だいぶ。
It's a black company, quite a lot.
ブラックだったんだ。大丈夫かな？
It was a black company. Is it okay?
この時代、ブラックまずいっすか。
Is "black company" bad in this day and age?
いやいやいや、メタバースですよね。
No no no, it's the Metaverse, right?
コンプライアンスありますからね。給料払い捲ってますよ。
There's compliance, you know. We're paying lots of salaries.
そうだっけ？ 給料...
Was it? Salaries...
はい、ということで今のオリジナル曲なんですけれども...
Yes, so, regarding the current original song...
なんと、なんと、なんとMVが作られておりますよ！
What, what, what, an MV is being made!
この後22時からAZKiチャンネルで公開されます！
It will be released on AZKi Channel from 22:00 today!
お願いしまーす！
Please check it out!
そして、そして...
And, and...
デジタル配信が、なんとこのあと24時から開始します！
Digital distribution will, what, start from 24:00 today!
いっぱい聴いてねー！
Please listen to it a lot!
本当念願の、マジで年単位で企画書書いたりとかして...
Really, the long-awaited... seriously, for years now, writing plans...
いっぱい喋って、みんなで準備してきました。
We've talked a lot and prepared together.
3DLIVE、念願叶えられましたね。
The 3D LIVE, our wish has been fulfilled.
やっと、この日が来たね。
Finally, this day has come.
ということで、僕からお二人に手紙を書いてきました。
So, I have written a letter to the two of you.
えっ！？ 聞いてません！ 社長！
Eh!? I haven't heard about this! CEO!
サプライズで。読んでくれるんですか？
As a surprise. Are you going to read it?
何、どんな手紙なんだ。真面目なやつを。
What kind of letter is it? A serious one.
本当かな？ 嘘言いながらじゃない？
Really? You're not just joking?
それでは、AZKiちゃんから。
Then, starting from AZKi-chan.
はい、じゃあ行きます。
Yes, here I go.
AZKiちゃんへ。かなけんに入ってくれて本当にありがとう。
To AZKi-chan. Thank you so much for joining Kanaken.
AZKiちゃんが率先して、コラボの案を出してくれたり...
It was a huge help that you took the lead in suggesting collab ideas...
かなけんでのオリ曲MVを進行してくれたり、本当に助かりました。
And managing the original song's MV for Kanaken.
AZKiちゃんへの信頼が、どんどん熱くなりまくりました。
My trust in you has become deeper and deeper.
本当に仕事人。ありがとう。
You're a true professional. Thank you.
活動のことを考えて交わすLINEは、めちゃめちゃ楽しいし...
The LINE messages I exchange while thinking about activities are fun...
一緒に音楽について話すのも、最高に幸せです。
And talking about music together makes me so happy.
AZKiちゃんへと出会えて、本当によかったです。
I'm so glad I met you.
これからもたくさん喋ろうね。いつもありがとう。
Let's keep talking a lot. Thank you, as always.
こちらこそありがとう。
Thank you too.
これからも末永くよろしくお願いします。
I look forward to our continued relationship for a long time.
ありがとう... 本当にいつもありがとう。
Thank you... Truly, thank you for everything.
坂又も！ ほしいよね、坂又も。
Sakamata too! You want one too, Sakamata.
坂又の分もあるよ。大事だよ。
I have one for Sakamata too. It's important.
実はあるから、読ませていただきます。
Actually, I have one, so I'll read it.
坂又へ。
To Sakamata.
かなけんで…
With Kanakenn...
何かやりたいねという始まりから…
Starting from wanting to do something together...
3Dライブができるまでに至るなんて、…
To reaching the point where we can do a 3D live...
思ってもいませんでした。
I never imagined it could happen.
そうだね。二人でマイクラをしてた時は想像もしていなかったと思います。
That's right. I don't think we could have imagined it when we were playing Minecraft together.
沙花叉は生意気な女ですが、…
Sakamata is a cheeky girl, but...
とても可愛い後輩で、…
...she's a very cute junior...
僕が活動のことで辛いことがあった時、…
...and when I was having a hard time with my activities...
あの、朝からねチャットして、LINEして。
...she'd chat and LINE me from the morning.
で、何かを察して、「お前は、…
And sensing something, she'd say, "You...
「ちょっと話す？」
Want to talk for a bit?"
…」と言ってよね。
...she'd say that.
言ったよね。
I did.
声をかけてくれて、2時間ぐらい喋ってくれたよね。
She reached out and talked to me for about two hours.
いや、なんかびっくりしてたよね。
No, you seemed surprised.
びっくりした！気づかれたんだと思って。
I was! I thought, "She noticed!"
本当にありましたよね、と。
That really happened.
気遣い屋さんなところに、いっぱい甘えさせてもらいました。
I've relied on her considerate nature a lot.
で、沙花叉がしんどい時とか寂しい時はね、
And when Sakamata is feeling down or lonely,
僕のこの大きな胸に甘えてください。
please rely on this big heart of mine.
ま、ないけど。
Well, you don't really have one...
ありますけれども！
I do too!
ないけど、でも本当に甘えてほしいと嬉しいなって思う。
Even so, I'd be really happy if you relied on me.
うん。そう言ってもらえたのが、このかなけんの期間で築いてきたことだよね。
Yeah. Being able to say that is something we've built during this Kanakenn period.
泣かないで、泣かないで！
Don't cry, don't cry!
こんな僕ですが、卒業までよろしく。
Even though I'm like this, please take care of me until graduation.
ずっと味方だよ。
I'll always be on your side.
泣かないで。ありがとうね。
Don't cry. Thank you.
ありがとうね。
Thank you.
お互い味方でいようね。
Let's stay on each other's side.
うん、ね。
Yeah, right.
泣いちゃった。
I ended up crying.
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
はい。ということで。
Yes. So...
実はですね、次で最後の曲に…
Uh, actually, the next song is...
次で最後。
The next one is the last.
なりますので。
...it will be.
ラストか。
The last one, huh.
ラスト、歌わせていただきたいと、思いますね。
We'd like to sing the last one.
はい。ということで。
Yes. So...
はい。それでは三人で、いきましょうか。
Yes. Well then, shall the three of us go?
せーの！
Ready, go!
Our Bright Parade!
Our Bright Parade
歌：天音かなた、沙花叉クロヱ、AZKi
Vocals: Amane Kanata, Sakamata Chloe, AZKi
作詞・作曲・編曲：堀江晶太
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Shota Horie
Our Bright Parade パレパレ 輝くんだよ
Our Bright Parade, pale-pale, it's shining
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling each other as a signal
パレパレパレ 探しにゆく
Pare-pare-pare, going to search
姿は何度も変わって
The appearance changes many times
まだ 独り言 綴った
Still wrote down my monologues
ただ 始まりたくて 走った
Just wanting it to start, I ran
遠く 暗がりに 灯った
Lit up in the distant darkness
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name far too dazzling
それは 優しすぎた思い出
That was a memory far too kind
もっと近づきたくて手を伸ばした
Wanted to get closer and reached out
思いがけず結びあった
Unexpectedly connected
ほら今 迷子は僕らになった
Look, now we've become the lost ones
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Pare-pare-pare, it's shining
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring along both the frustration and the love
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき日差し
A modest prayer is light, endless sunshine
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of
ここから これから
From here, from now on
Our Bright Parade パレ
Our Bright Parade, parade
Story...
数え切れない言の葉
Countless words
数えるような想いじゃないさ
It's not a feeling you can count
ほら 今 僕らを一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one
Parade Parade Parade
美しいんだよ
It's beautiful
許し合える刹那
A moment of mutual forgiveness
夜はきらめく
The night glitters
雨 晴れ 彼
Rain, sun, he
また同じ空
Under the same sky again
ふさわしい日々を
The appropriate days
君と歩くことさ
Are walking with you
君と歩くことなんだ
It's all about walking with you
ただいまを聞けば
If I hear "I'm home"
おかえりって叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back"
当たり前じゃないさ
It's not a given
Parade Parade Parade
輝くんだよ
It shines
暗がりを満たすのは
What fills the darkness
君が僕だ
Is you and me
Parade Parade Parade
輝くんだよ
It shines
悔しさも愛おしさも
Both frustration and affection
連れておいで
Bring them along
風 夢 羽
Wind, dreams, wings
飛び立てるさ
We can take flight
ささやかな祈りに光
Light in a humble prayer
終わりなき日差し
Endless sunshine
君と飛び込んで行く
Diving in with you
素敵な世界さ
It's a wonderful world
ここからこれから
From here, from now on
Our Bright Parade Parade
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
楽しかったよー！
That was fun!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
また遊ぼうねー！
Let's play again!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
またねー！
See you again!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!